<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Themes on Hugo</title>
    <link>https://gohugo.io/categories/themes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Themes on Hugo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gohugo.io/categories/themes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Theme</title>
      <link>https://gohugo.io/themes/creating/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo.io/themes/creating/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re creating a theme with plans to share it on the Hugo Themes website please note that your theme&amp;rsquo;s demo will be available in a sub-directory of website and for the theme&amp;rsquo;s assets to load properly you will need to create absolute paths in the templates by using either the absURL function or .Permalink. Also make sure not to use a forward slash / in the beginning of a PATH, because Hugo will turn it into a relative URL and the absURL function will have no effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install and Use Themes</title>
      <link>https://gohugo.io/themes/installing-and-using-themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo.io/themes/installing-and-using-themes/</guid>
      <description>Hugo currently doesn’t ship with a “default” theme. This decision is intentional. We leave it up to you to decide which theme best suits your Hugo project.
  Assumptions  You have already installed Hugo on your development machine. You have git installed on your machine and you are familiar with basic git usage.  Install Themes   The community-contributed themes featured on themes.gohugo.io are hosted in a centralized GitHub repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Components</title>
      <link>https://gohugo.io/themes/theme-components/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo.io/themes/theme-components/</guid>
      <description>Since Hugo 0.42 a project can configure a theme as a composite of as many theme components you need:
config. yaml&amp;nbsp; toml&amp;nbsp; json&amp;nbsp;  theme:-my-shortcodes-base-theme-hyde   theme = [&amp;#34;my-shortcodes&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;base-theme&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;hyde&amp;#34;]    { &amp;#34;theme&amp;#34;: [ &amp;#34;my-shortcodes&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;base-theme&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;hyde&amp;#34; ] }      You can even nest this, and have the theme component itself include theme components in its own config.toml (theme inheritance).1
The theme definition example above in config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Themes</title>
      <link>https://gohugo.io/themes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo.io/themes/</guid>
      <description>Hugo provides a robust theming system that is easy to implement yet feature complete. You can view the themes created by the Hugo community on the Hugo themes website.
Hugo themes are powered by the excellent Go template library and are designed to reduce code duplication. They are easy to both customize and keep in synch with the upstream theme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>